## Celia Diller

Atlanta, GA • celiardiller@gmail.com • (706) 512 – 5489

## **SUMMARY**

Bachelor of Business and Biology student experienced in customer service with a history of working in varied industries. Progressive in investigating the integration of multiple disciplines to create an improved realm of problem-solving in the workplace.

## **EDUCATION**

# St. Lawrence University - Canton, NY

August 2016 – May 2020

# Bachelor of Science in Biology and Business in the Liberal Arts

Competitive Member of Varsity Riding Team- August 2016 to March 2020

#### RELEVANT COURSES

- Financial & Managerial Accounting
- Microeconomics & Macroeconomics
- Direct & Indirect Marketing
- Leadership & Public Relations
- Lab Animals
- Cell Biology Research Methods

#### SKILLS

- Public Speaking & Communication
- 8+ Years of Customer Service Experience
- Social Media Management & Marketing
- Adobe XD, Procreate, Microsoft Products, Photoshop.
- Handling Lab Animals
- Cell Biology Lab Experience

# **Career-Foundry**

March 2021 – December 2021

## **UI Designer- Specialization in Frontend Development for Designers**

An Intensive training program for UI Designers

The course is an intensive study program that navigates through the world of UI Design with specific individual tasks with mentor and tutor feedback.

- Coding in HTML
- User Interviews
- User Persona, Stories, Flows
- Creating Brands

- Wireframing
- Prototyping
- Competitive Analysis
- Achieve Business Requirements

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### The Desoto Theatre - Rome, GA

September 2020 – December 2021

## **Social Media Marketing Intern and Fundraising Consultant**

- Created marketing strategies for the Board to use to boost ticket sales for various events.
- Excelled at creating visual content (Instagram posts/stories, Facebook posts, videos, and slideshows) to increase donations and grants that will be used for renovations of the theatre.
- Created and presented to supervisor over a dozen verbal and visual presentations to be used in Board Meetings.
- Re-organized newspaper clippings and photos in chronological order for Board members to have effortless access.

## Sunflour Community Bakery - Rome, GA

June 2019 – February 2020

## **UI Designer and Business Developmental Intern**

- Created, themed and designed the company's website and continued to create brand ideas.
- Undertook a direct marketing role by promoting the company through farmers markets and sales in the bakery.
- Excelled at an indirect marketing role by designing an aesthetically attractive website and social media presence in the community.
- Mastered the point-of-sale system (Clover) by handling set up of the system, maintaining online orders, adding/editing inventory, adding new employees and editing rewards systems for consumers.
- Greeted guests, addressed in-house issues, and managed over the phone transactions.

## Brewer Bookstore - Canton, NY

August 2016 – March 2020

#### **Barista / Sales Associate**

- Obtained advanced knowledge about coffee/tea blends and different coffee drinks.
- Added new product ideas, organizational support and analytical skills to the bookstore team.
- Innovated new coffee drinks and prepared the pastry case in an aesthetically pleasing way.
- Trained new student workers the point-of-sale system and taught the products we provide in the cafe.
- Obtained great multitasking skills in a high fast-paced environment.